[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "1/1=",
    "answer": 2,
    "rank": 90,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "2/1=",
    "answer": 3,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "3/1=",
    "answer": 4,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "4/1=",
    "answer": 5,
    "rank": 95,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "5/1=",
    "answer": 6,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "6/3=",
    "answer": 9,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "6/6=",
    "answer": 12,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "6/19=",
    "answer": 25,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "16/11=",
    "answer": 27,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "93/23=",
    "answer": 116,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "question": "84/21=",
    "answer": 105,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "question": "79/83=",
    "answer": 162,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "question": "4/73=",
    "answer": 77,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "question": "57/91=",
    "answer": 148,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "question": "78/34=",
    "answer": 112,
    "rank": 95,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "question": "74/11=",
    "answer": 85,
    "rank": 95,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "question": "41/5=",
    "answer": 46,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "question": "40/21=",
    "answer": 61,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "question": "63/38=",
    "answer": 101,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "71/81=",
    "answer": 152,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "93/89=",
    "answer": 182,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "14/34=",
    "answer": 48,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "72/50=",
    "answer": 122,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "32/57=",
    "answer": 89,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "69/62=",
    "answer": 131,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "42/55=",
    "answer": 97,
    "rank": 95,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "69/83=",
    "answer": 152,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "40/58=",
    "answer": 98,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "43/31=",
    "answer": 74,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "question": "47/87=",
    "answer": 134,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "question": "14/56=",
    "answer": 70,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "question": "64/10=",
    "answer": 74,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "question": "70/63=",
    "answer": 133,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "question": "60/69=",
    "answer": 129,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "question": "78/53=",
    "answer": 131,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "question": "70/27=",
    "answer": 97,
    "rank": 90,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "question": "59/97=",
    "answer": 156,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "question": "59/41=",
    "answer": 100,
    "rank": 105,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "question": "70/61=",
    "answer": 131,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "28/66=",
    "answer": 94,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "32/93=",
    "answer": 125,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "19/27=",
    "answer": 46,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "85/32=",
    "answer": 117,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "94/7=",
    "answer": 101,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "95/18=",
    "answer": 113,
    "rank": 95,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "69/30=",
    "answer": 99,
    "rank": 95,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "54/47=",
    "answer": 101,
    "rank": 95,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "68/57=",
    "answer": 125,
    "rank": 95,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "90/81=",
    "answer": 171,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "question": "62/29=",
    "answer": 91,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "question": "9/40=",
    "answer": 49,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "question": "75/58=",
    "answer": 133,
    "rank": 105,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "question": "14/92=",
    "answer": 106,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "question": "93/38=",
    "answer": 131,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "question": "62/99=",
    "answer": 161,
    "rank": 105,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "question": "53/71=",
    "answer": 124,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "question": "4/77=",
    "answer": 81,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "question": "50/68=",
    "answer": 118,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "question": "55/80=",
    "answer": 135,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  },
  {
    "id": 61,
    "question": "1234/6548",
    "answer": 7782,
    "rank": 100,
    "category": "divide"
  }
]
